lumioapp.com 2018-04-01

# Privacy policy

Effective date: 8 March 2017

We take the privacy of our users very seriously. We use our best endeavors to keep all your data safe and secure and we never sell your data, neither your email address, nor any information on how you use lumio.

The lumio Chrome extension in beta saves whatever you save with lumio to your own account. Noone else has access to it other than you.

Nevertheless, we do collect certain information – as described below – and when you start using lumio, you agree to our collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Use](https://www.lumioapp.com/terms-of-use).

## 1\. Information we collect

When signing up for the service on the lumio website, we ask you to provide your email address.

We may collect information about how and when you use lumio. This information include your IP address, time, date, browser used, and the actions taken by you within the application.

We may collect information on your exchange of information with our customer support team.

## 2\. Use of information collected

We use all information collected to perform and to further improve the services requested.

We will use your email address to communicate with you about the service. You can stop receiving our emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in every email.

We use the information on how and when you use lumio to enhance your lumio experience. When such information is used in any other way, it will be in aggregated form with all personal identification removed.

We use customer support information for product development purposes. We may also store them for quality assurance purposes.

We do not share, sell, rent, or trade any information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

We may disclose your information if we believe it’s necessary in order to comply with the law, such as to comply with a subpoena, regulation or legal request, respond to a government request, to address fraud or security issues, to protect the safety of any person, or to protect our own rights or property.

## 3\. Security

We use our best endeavors to protect all information stored within our databases and we restrict access to information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions.

Nevertheless, nobody is 100% safe from hackers. In the case of any security breach in our databases we will notify you as soon as possible and will also inform you about the actions taken by us in response.

## 4\. Changes in our privacy policy

From time to time, we may modify our Privacy Policy. If we do so, we will let you know either by posting the modified Privacy Policy on the lumio website or through other communications. It’s important that you review the modified Privacy Policy because if you continue to use the service after we have let you know that the Privacy Policy has been modified, you are indicating to us that you agree to be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

## 5\. Feedback

We welcome and appreciate all feedback, comments and suggestions in relation to the service. Please share your feedback with us at lumio@lumioapp.com If you provide us any feedback, you agree that we may use, copy, modify, create derivative works of and otherwise exploit the feedback for any purpose.

## 6\. Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at lumio@lumioapp.com.
